eyeonspain.com 2010-05-26

# Eye on Spain privacy policy

#### Privacy policy

We are committed to protecting your privacy at eyeonspain.com. We will not collect any personal information from you that you do not volunteer, and we are the sole owner of all information collected on this site. We do not sell, share, or rent this information to others in any way that we have not mentioned in this statement. 

**Cookies**

Like many other Web sites, eyeonspain.com uses cookies to identify members so they don't have to re-enter a user id and password when they, for example, wish to post to a discussion. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. (Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site.) We use session ID cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. Cookies also help us improve your experience and display more prominently goods and services that might interest you. If you do not have cookies enabled, you must enter your password each time you access our site or any of its member features. 

**Legal Disclaimer**

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. 

**Third parties**

eyeonSpain.com may provide third parties with aggregate statistics about our customers, traffic patterns, and related site information. This data reflects site usage patterns gathered during thousands of customer visits to our Web site each month but does not contain behavioral or identifying information about any individual member, unless that member has given us permission to share that information.  eyeonspain.com also may use third party companies to provide delivery of e-mail newsletters and other messages over e-mail. Also be aware that we may buy and sell business assets and/or divisions; customer information is generally part of such a sale. 

**Links**

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, eyeonspain.com, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Message Boards and Public Forums**

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online \- for example on message boards, through e-mail, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others.  In short, by posting personal information online that is publicly accessible, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. 

**Security**

We use reasonable precautions to keep the personal information you disclose both in your browsing and your purchases and to only release this information to third parties we believe share our commitment to privacy. However, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for the actions of these parties. 

**Obtaining your consent**

By using our Web site, you give eyeonspain.com permission to collect information about the pages served to you as an anonymous user for the purpose of calculating aggregate site statistics. If you register at eyeonspain.com, you authorize eyeonspain.com to use information you provide to personalise the information we deliver to you and to use your demographic information when calculating aggregate customer data. eyeonspain.com may occasionally amend this policy. We suggest that you bookmark this page and check to see if it has changed from time to time, although we will inform all registered members of any changes as soon as they are made. 

**Google Advertising Cookies**

* Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html). 

**Questions?**

If you wish to change any information you have given us, or have any questions on our Privacy Policy, you can contact us at feedback @ eyeonspain.com (remove the spaces in the email address).
